<oryx><HTTP><code>200</code><message>OK</message></HTTP><info><homepage>1</homepage><pagetitle>TechCrunch - The latest technology news and information on startups</pagetitle><favicon>http://s1.wp.com/wp-content/themes/vip/techcrunch-2013/assets/images/favicon.ico?m=1381204869g</favicon></info><post><item><published>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 11:34:24 +0000</published><title>Primo Is An Arduino Robot That Teaches Kids Programming Logic Through Play</title><link>http://techcrunch.com/2013/11/24/primo/</link><image>http://tctechcrunch2011.files.wordpress.com/2013/11/primo.jpg?w=210&amp;h=158&amp;crop=1</image><summary>Meet Primo: a physical programming interface that teaches children programming logic while they control the movements of an Arduino-powered robot. All of Primo's electronics are concealed inside wooden boxes, so from the child's point of view they're playing with blocks,</summary></item><item><published>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 06:14:33 +0000</published><title>Sheet Music App Tonara Adds Interactive Score Synchronization To Help Musicians And Stage Techs</title><link>http://techcrunch.com/2013/11/23/tonara-score-sync/</link><image>http://tctechcrunch2011.files.wordpress.com/2013/11/screen-shot-2013-11-24-at-2-07-06-pm.png?w=210&amp;h=158&amp;crop=1</image><summary>Tonara, the interactive sheet music app, has announced a new score synchronization feature for its iPad app. One of Tonara's most important updates, score synchronization can now help musicians review their practice sessions and, in the future, will power stage</summary></item><item><published>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 04:46:41 +0000</published><title>Fully-Automated Ad Management Startup Multichannel Raises $3M In Seed Funding</title><link>http://techcrunch.com/2013/11/23/multichannel-hk/</link><image>http://tctechcrunch2011.files.wordpress.com/2013/11/mcdashboard.jpeg?w=210&amp;h=158&amp;crop=1</image><summary>Multichannel wants to help marketers fully automate their online advertising so they can focus on developing campaigns instead of staring at software dashboards all day. Based in Hong Kong and the U.S., Multichannel has raised $3 million in seed funding</summary></item><item><published>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 02:00:23 +0000</published><title>The Battle For The Connected Home Is Heating Up</title><link>http://techcrunch.com/2013/11/23/big-companies-could-crowd-out-startups-in-the-new-battle-for-the-home/</link><image>http://tctechcrunch2011.files.wordpress.com/2013/11/newbattle.jpg?w=210&amp;h=158&amp;crop=1</image><summary>With the emergence of connected devices, the entire home is being reinvented as a data product, opening great opportunities to entrepreneurs. A whole new generation of startups is rushing in. Nest, with its beautifully-designed home products, has become the poster</summary></item><item><published>Sun, 24 Nov 2013 00:21:14 +0000</published><title>Big Insurance Can Now Bypass Obamacare Website, Tech Companies Still Waiting</title><link>http://techcrunch.com/2013/11/23/big-insurance-can-now-bypass-obamacare-website-tech-companies-still-waiting/</link><image>http://tctechcrunch2011.files.wordpress.com/2013/11/4485359963_eb54f361d0_z.jpg?w=210&amp;h=158&amp;crop=1</image><summary>As the federal government struggles to regain hope that it can get enough consumers to buy health insurance, it is piloting an option for consumers to purchase insurance outside of state websites. Consumers in three states, Florida, Texas, and Ohio,</summary></item><item><published>Sat, 23 Nov 2013 23:09:47 +0000</published><title>CrunchWeek: The Xbox One &amp; Playstation 4, The Rise Of QuizUp, The Fall Of Turntable.fm</title><link>http://techcrunch.com/2013/11/23/crunchweek-the-new-xbox-one-playstation-4-quizups-quick-rise-the-fall-of-turntable-fm/</link><image/><summary>It's time for a new episode of CrunchWeek, the show in which a few of us writers sit ourselves down in front of a few TechCrunch TV cameras to discuss the most interesting news stories from the past seven days</summary></item><item><published>Sat, 23 Nov 2013 19:00:57 +0000</published><title>Daric, A New Peer To Peer Lending Platform, Will Go Live Next Week</title><link>http://techcrunch.com/2013/11/23/daric-a-new-peer-to-peer-lending-platform-will-go-live-next-week/</link><image>http://tctechcrunch2011.files.wordpress.com/2013/11/daric_screenshot1.png?w=210&amp;h=158&amp;crop=1</image><summary>Daric, a new peer to peer lending platform, will launch next week as a place for individuals and small businesses to obtain loans, and a place for lenders to see up to 9-10% returns on their investments. Individuals will be</summary></item><item><published>Sat, 23 Nov 2013 19:00:07 +0000</published><title>Down, The App Formerly Known As Bang With Friends, Relaunches On The iPhone</title><link>http://techcrunch.com/2013/11/23/down-ios/</link><image>http://tctechcrunch2011.files.wordpress.com/2013/11/down.png?w=210&amp;h=158&amp;crop=1</image><summary>Following a trademark dispute with Zynga, the team behind the hookup app Bang With Friends rebranded as Down, adjusted their approach, and launched on Android. Now those changes have come to iOS as well, with an update that was quietly</summary></item><item><published>Sat, 23 Nov 2013 18:00:41 +0000</published><title>Gillmor Gang: Dreamforce 2013 Live</title><link>http://techcrunch.com/2013/11/23/gillmor-gang-dreamforce-2013-live/</link><image>http://tctechcrunch2011.files.wordpress.com/2011/04/gillmor-gang-test-pattern_excerpt.jpeg?w=210&amp;h=151&amp;crop=1</image><summary>The Gillmor Gang — Robert Scoble, Adam Bosworth, John Taschek, John Rymer, and Steve Gillmor — gathered at Dreamforce 2013 to celebrate what @scobleizer called the maturing of mobile. On the Salesforce Live TV set, it was hard to hear</summary></item><item><published>Sat, 23 Nov 2013 17:30:36 +0000</published><title>NSA Has 50,000 ‘Digital Sleeper Agents' Via Computer Malware, Says Latest Snowden Leak</title><link>http://techcrunch.com/2013/11/23/nsa-has-50000-digital-sleeper-agents-snowden/</link><image>http://tctechcrunch2011.files.wordpress.com/2013/07/nsa-verizon-phone-records-jpeg1-1280x960.jpg?w=210&amp;h=158&amp;crop=1</image><summary>Sleeper agents are among the most sinister spy assets: they lie in wait, wolves in sheeps clothing, and then deliver a critical blow when activated. The NSA has 50,000 of those waiting for the literal push of a button, according</summary></item><item><published>Sat, 23 Nov 2013 16:28:21 +0000</published><title>Couric Get Would Mean Yet Another Chase Of The Online Video Carrot For Yahoo</title><link>http://techcrunch.com/2013/11/23/yahoo-katie-couric-show/</link><image>http://tctechcrunch2011.files.wordpress.com/2013/11/yahoo-couric.jpg?w=210&amp;h=158&amp;crop=1</image><summary>Yahoo is reportedly going to make its Katie Couric-hosted talk show on Monday, according to a new report from AllThingsD's Kara Swisher, supported by an earlier article from the NYT. Swisher is known for having an inside track on Yahoo</summary></item><item><published>Sat, 23 Nov 2013 14:04:44 +0000</published><title>Patent Application For Touch ID Shows How Apple Secures Fingerprint Information On iPhone 5s</title><link>http://techcrunch.com/2013/11/23/apple-touch-id-patent-application/</link><image>http://tctechcrunch2011.files.wordpress.com/2013/09/touch-id.png?w=210&amp;h=158&amp;crop=1</image><summary>A new patent application published by the USPTO (via MacRumors) shows some more detail around Apple's use of Touch ID and the fingerprint sensor in the iPhone 5s. Apple has been mostly quiet about the specifics of how the tech</summary></item><item><published>Sat, 23 Nov 2013 14:00:32 +0000</published><title>Let's Kill The Aid Industry</title><link>http://techcrunch.com/2013/11/23/lets-kill-the-aid-industry/</link><image>http://tctechcrunch2011.files.wordpress.com/2013/11/un-aid.jpg?w=210&amp;h=158&amp;crop=1</image><summary>Long have I nursed a healthy contempt for the aid industry. As I spent much of a decade wandering around the planet, taking local public transit through poor and/or unstable nations, I kept encountering aid workers in their flashy white</summary></item><item><published>Sat, 23 Nov 2013 13:53:19 +0000</published><title>Gift Guide: For The Tech-Happy Fashionista</title><link>http://techcrunch.com/2013/11/23/gift-guide-for-the-tech-happy-fashionista/</link><image>http://tctechcrunch2011.files.wordpress.com/2013/11/frends_taylor_-minkoff-11.jpg?w=210&amp;h=158&amp;crop=1</image><summary>The holidays truly are the most magical time of the year. The twinkly lights, the spiked eggnog... the designer collaborations on your favorite tech products. It warms the heart.</summary></item><item><published>Sat, 23 Nov 2013 08:59:21 +0000</published><title>The AUUG iPhone Grip And App Turns Your Body Into A Musical Instrument</title><link>http://techcrunch.com/2013/11/23/the-auug-iphone-grip-and-app-turns-your-body-into-a-musical-instrument/</link><image>http://tctechcrunch2011.files.wordpress.com/2013/11/auug.jpg?w=210&amp;h=158&amp;crop=1</image><summary>Anything that encourages people to stop hunching over their iPhones like a tech-literate Mr. Burns is a good thing--especially when it also looks cool and makes fun noises. The AUUG Motion Synth, a grip that attaches to your iPhone or</summary></item><item><published>Sat, 23 Nov 2013 08:04:57 +0000</published><title>Coursera Adds Another $20M To Its Already Massive Series B</title><link>http://techcrunch.com/2013/11/23/coursera-adds-another-20m-to-its-already-massive-series-b/</link><image>http://tctechcrunch2011.files.wordpress.com/2013/11/screen-shot-2013-11-23-at-4-00-26-pm.png?w=210&amp;h=158&amp;crop=1</image><summary>Back in July, Coursera announced a $43 million series B. Now the round has grown to an even more impressive $63 million with the addition of funding from three undisclosed university partners.</summary></item><item><published>Sat, 23 Nov 2013 05:00:47 +0000</published><title>Email Is Now Just Another Stream</title><link>http://techcrunch.com/2013/11/22/email-is-now-just-another-stream/</link><image>http://tctechcrunch2011.files.wordpress.com/2013/11/streams4.png?w=210&amp;h=158&amp;crop=1</image><summary>Editors note: Peter Yared is the CTO/CIO at CBS Interactive. Follow him on Twitter @peteryared. Only a couple of years ago, pundits were predicting an end to email. But instead of fading away, there’s been ever-increasing email volume and usage.</summary></item><item><published>Sat, 23 Nov 2013 05:00:19 +0000</published><title>Geeks for Monarchy: The Rise of the Neoreactionaries</title><link>http://techcrunch.com/2013/11/22/geeks-for-monarchy/</link><image>http://tctechcrunch2011.files.wordpress.com/2013/11/king-statue.jpg?w=210&amp;h=158&amp;crop=1</image><summary>Many of us yearn for a return to one golden age or another. But there's a community of bloggers taking the idea to an extreme: they want to turn the dial way back to the days before the French Revolution.</summary></item><item><published>Sat, 23 Nov 2013 01:56:31 +0000</published><title>Microsoft Matches PS4 Sales With 1 Million Xbox Ones In 24 Hours, But Takes 11 More Countries To Do It</title><link>http://techcrunch.com/2013/11/22/microsoft-matches-ps4-sales-with-1-million-xbox-ones-in-24-hours-but-takes-11-more-countries-to-do-it/</link><image>http://tctechcrunch2011.files.wordpress.com/2013/11/gx8a0692.jpg?w=210&amp;h=158&amp;crop=1</image><summary>Microsoft sent out some Xbox One PR today to various outlets, you may have seen the numbers. Over 1 million Xbox One (our review) consoles sold within 24 hours! Thats pretty good, and far better than the Xbox 360 sold</summary></item><item><published>Sat, 23 Nov 2013 00:37:28 +0000</published><title>Microsoft's Julie Larson-Green Hints At Further Windows Harmonization Across Device Classes</title><link>http://techcrunch.com/2013/11/22/microsofts-julie-larson-green-hints-at-further-windows-harmonization-across-device-classes/</link><image>http://tctechcrunch2011.files.wordpress.com/2013/11/2013-11-22_16h10_57.jpg?w=210&amp;h=158&amp;crop=1</image><summary>A recent CITEworld article written by Mary Branscombe includes a quote from a Microsoft leader that directly hints at future harmonization of the various strains of Windows across disparate device classes. According to Branscombe, Microsoft executive vice president Julie Larson-Green</summary></item></post></oryx>